prize.com 2012-12-10

# Win Cash and Prizes Playing Games - Prize.com

PRIVACY POLICY

    ## Effective: March 8, 2012

    Prize, LLC ("us," "we," or "our") is committed to your privacy. As part of the normal operation of our skill gaming and community services, we collect and, in some cases, may disclose information about you.  We have created the following Privacy Policy to let you know what information we collect when you visit our website located at www.Prize.com (the "Website"), why we collect it, and how it is used.
    
    This Privacy Policy describes, among other things, the types of information collected about you when you visit the Website, how your information may be used and when it may be disclosed; how you can control the use of and disclosure of your information; and how your information is protected. 
    
    This Privacy Policy is governed by our [Terms and Conditions](http://www.prize.com/terms).  By using our Website and the services therein, you consent to the terms of our current Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions. We reserve the right to change the Privacy Policy at any time. For more information please refer to the paragraph entitled "Changes to this Privacy Policy" detailed below. If you believe we have not adhered to this Privacy Policy or if you have any other questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please go to our [Support Center](http://www.prize.com/support).
    
    Prize, LLC has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information.  The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software.   TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at privacy@prize.com.  If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request). The TRUSTe certification only applies to information collected on our Web site www.prize.com and does not cover information collected through other means (such as offline, through mobile devices or third party services). 

    ## 1.  SCOPE OF PRIVACY POLICY

    This Privacy Policy applies to all information that you provide to us and that we maintain electronically, whether you provide the information through our Website, or through other means. Additionally, this Privacy Policy applies to any Personal Information (defined below) obtained from your use of the Website, or through other means. 
    
    This Privacy Policy does not apply to any information that you may provide to third parties; for example, other websites linked to this Website. If you access our Website from a third party Social Networking Site ("SNS"), you may be required to also read and accept the SNS Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of those websites, and you should contact such third parties directly to determine their respective privacy policies.

    ## 2.  INFORMATION COLLECTED

    In order to operate the Website and provide you with access to certain services that we offer through the Website, we collect the following types of information from you: (i) personal information by which you may be identified ("Personal Information") and (ii) information about you and your activities on the Website that does not identify you personally ("General Information"), such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, domain server, the type of computer, web browser, operating system or platform you use and referrer data identifying the web pages you visited prior to and after visiting our Website, your movement and activity within the Website and your geographic location.
    
    	**A.	PERSONAL INFORMATION**
    
    	**_Personal Information about You We Collect Directly from You_**
    
    	We collect your Personal Information when you provide it to us when you interact with us directly through our Website, such as when you create an account, access various content or features, contact us directly, post comments on our blog, chat room, bulletin boards, or other areas of the Website in which you or other parties create, store or post any content messages, comments, materials or other items, or otherwise interact with our Website. The Personal Information we collect and maintain about you includes:

  * Contact information, such as name, e-mail address, postal address, and telephone numbers;
  * Date of birth;
  * Gender;
  * Your country and city ("current location"); and
  * In limited circumstances, payment and identity verification information, such as credit card number, billing address, social security number or comparable national identifiers, a image of your driver's license and/or driver's license number where needed for withdrawals and/or billing purposed when we need to charge you for the use of your account or to access a particular service (e.g., contests).

    	In order to provide a fair playing environment for all users and to protect the integrity of the Website, we also collect Personal Information such as browsing and gaming habbits which we use to investigate complaints of cheating or behavior that we believe may be contrary to the Terms and Conditions. By partaking in the services we provide, you agree that we can monitor your computer closely to detect any attempt to cheat, abuse, or any other form of malicious act that may harm or disrupt the fair environment we are trying to provide for our users. This may include screenshots of players' computer desktops or footage of in-game play. You also agree that we may make use of "Active X" controls.
    	
    	Certain information about your activity on the Website is not itself Personal Information (e.g., information about your game play preferences) but may be linked to your account information. For instance, the following information ("Gamer Information") is publicly displayed on the Site and, provided it does not identify you personally, shall not be considered to Personal Information:

  * Your username;
  * Game scores;
  * Game, contests and tournament records on the website;
  * Game, achievements and awards;
  * How long and often you visit the Website;
  * Your favorite games;
  * Your skill rating;
  * Winnings from contests and tournaments; and
  * Any personal information you choose to disclose in Your public profile, a chat window or discussion forums on the Website.

    	**_Personal Information about You Received from other Sources_**
    	
    	Where permitted by applicable law, we may collect information about you from other sources, including through interactive applications (such as mobile devices and third-party services), from commercially available sources (such as data aggregators and public databases) and when you access our Website through an SNS. We may access and store some or all of the following Personal Information:

  * Contact information, such as name, e-mail address, postal address, and telephone numbers;
  * Age and date of birth;
  * Gender; and
  * Personal interests.

    	The information you allow us to access varies by source and SNS platform, and it is affected by the privacy settings established by those third parties. This privacy policy does not cover the practices of third parties, including those that may disclose information to us. For more information about how those third parties handle your Personal Information, please refer to their privacy policies.
        
    	**_Facebook Connect or other OpenID provider_**
        
    	You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form.  Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.   
    
    	**_Social Media (Features) and Widgets:_**
    
    	Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 
     	
    	**B.	GENERAL INFORMATION**
    	
    	In addition to collecting Personal Information from you, we, our parent, affiliates, subsidiaries and Partners and our third party service providers may use a variety of technologies that automatically collect General Information. General Information is information about you or your activities on our Website that do not identify you personally. This includes your IP address, domain server, the type of computer, web browser, operating system or platform you use and referrer data identifying the web pages you visited prior to and after visiting our Website, your movement and activity within the Website and your geographic location. The methods used to collect this information may include: 

  * **Cookies.** The Website may place small files, called "cookies" onto your computer. Cookies are data files that websites write onto computer hard drives for record keeping purposes when you visit them. The cookie file then identifies you as a unique user. Cookies make your use of this Website more pleasing and efficient by "personalizing" your Website experience and gathering Website statistical data, such as which parts of the Website you have previously visited, what material you downloaded, your Internet provider's domain name and country, and the addresses of websites you visited immediately before and after our Website. They enable us to tailor the information you receive and to assist our Partners or other third party organizations with whom we have strategic alliances by identifying you as our customer or Website user. For instance, we will use a cookie to ensure you only have to type in your user name the first time you visit the Website, if you choose to activate the "remember me" function under the login box. Another use of cookies can be to serve advertising banners for our services to you. These banners may be served by us or by a third party on our behalf. Although most web browsers automatically accept cookies, you can sometimes change your browser to prevent cookies or to notify you when you are sent a cookie. Cookies are not required of you to access the Website or to use our services. They just help us make your visit to the Website the best it can be. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personal information you submit while on our site. The use of cookies by third parties is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies.
  * **Web Beacons.** Small graphic images or web programming code called web beacons (also known as "pixel tags" or "clear GIFs") may be included on the pages of the Website and in email messages we send you. Web beacons or other similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes, such as to count visitors to the Website, monitor how you navigate the Website or to count how many particular articles or links posted on the Website were actually viewed. Web beacons may also be employed by our third party tracking utility partner to help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers' personal information.
  * **Embedded Scripts.** An embedded script is programming code designed to collect information about your use of this Website, such as the links you click on. The code is temporarily downloaded to your computer from our web server or a third party provider, is active only while you are connected to the Website and is deactivated or deleted once you leave the Website. 

    ## 3.  HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

    We use your information procured and maintained above for things that may include, but are not limited to, the following:

  * Allow you to participate in features we offer on the Website;
  * Set up an account for the site as well as the support section of the site;
  * Send you welcoming emails when you register for the site or support section of the site;
  * Process your registration, including, at time, verifying that the e-mail address you provide is active and valid;
  * Enable you to participate in features such as skill game contests and message boards;
  * Fulfill your requests for products, services, and information, including to authorize a purchase, and complete a transaction that you have requested;
  * Process awards payment and business requests related to contest participation;
  * To respond to your inquiries;
  * Provide customer services and resolve any complaints; 
  * Communicate with you regarding certain products, services or promotions offered by us or our Partners, provided that you have not already opted out of receiving such communications;
  * Cross-reference with other Personal Information that we have acquired about you or may acquire about you through other sources;
  * Improve our Website and resolve any technical problems;
  * Analyze the use of Website and information about visitors to our Website to understand and improve our service offerings and, in accordance with our sharing policies, discussed below, to produce anonymous or aggregated data and statistics that might help third parties develop their own products and service offerings;
  * Ensure that you and other users on the Website that are playing our games are playing fair. 
  * Customize the content you see when you visit the Website, including to develop and provide advertising tailored to your interests;
  * Ensure compliance with the our [Terms and Conditions](http://www.prize.com/terms); 
  * Comply with any applicable laws and regulations; and
  * For any other purposes disclosed to you at the time we collect your information or pursuant to your consent.

    We may provide your information to government officials and agencies as required by law, and Partners as part of business operations, transaction processing, and marketing efforts, as identified below.  For purposes of this Privacy Policy, "Partner" shall mean any person or entity with whom we enter into any kind of business transaction who is under an obligation to us to use reasonable care to keep Personal Information confidential.

    ## 4.  DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT

    We are committed to maintaining your trust and we want you to understand when and with whom we may share information collected about you. We may share General Information, such as aggregate user statistics, with our Partners and non-affiliated third parties. We may provide data, including Personal Information about you, with our parent, affiliates, subsidiaries and Partners. We may also share your Personal Information as disclosed at the time your provide your Personal Information, as set forth in the Privacy Policy and in the following circumstances:

  * **Third Party Service Providers.** In some cases we may employ third party service providers to perform certain services on our behalf, including, without limitation: (i) processing and fulfilling your orders (including payments); (ii) providing customer service; (iii) shipping, sending postal mail and e-mails; (iv) repetitive information from customer lists; (v) analyzing, updating and correcting information we receive on the Website; (vi) performing business analysis or quality control; (vii) providing marketing assistance, search results and links (including, without limitation, paid listings and links) and (viii) processing credit card and debit card payments. Consequently, we may share your Personal Information with these third party service providers if they need it to perform services on our behalf. However, such third party service providers are not authorized by us to use your Personal Information for any other purpose. 
  * **Contests and Promotions.** The Website may offer contests and other promotions that may require registration. If you choose to enter a contest or promotion, your Personal Information may be disclosed to third parties in connection with the administration of such offering, such as in connection with winner selection, prize fulfillment, and as required by law, such as on a winners list. By entering a contest or promotion, you are agreeing to the official rules that govern that offering, which may contain specific requirements of you, including, except where prohibited by law, allowing us and/or other parties to use your name, voice and/or likeness in advertising or marketing materials.
  * **Disclosure of Customer Information for Legal and Administrative Reasons.** We may disclose your Personal Information without notice: (i) when required by law or to comply with a court order, subpoena, search warrant or other legal process; (ii) to cooperate in investigations of fraud, intellectual property infringement or any other activity that is illegal or may expose us or you to legal liability; (iii) to comply with legal, regulatory or administrative requirements of governmental authorities (including, without limitation, requests from the governmental agency authorities to view your Personal Information); (iv) to protect and defend the rights, property or safety of us, our subsidiaries and affiliates and any of their officers, directors, employees, attorneys, agents, contractors and partners, and the Website's users; (v) to enforce or apply the Website's Terms and Conditions; and (iv) to verify the identity of the Website's users, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.
  * **Business Transfers.** Your Personal Information may be transferred, sold or otherwise conveyed ("Conveyed") to a third party where we: (i) merge with or are acquired by another business entity; (ii) sell all or substantially all of our assets; (iii) is adjudicated bankrupt or (iv) is liquidated or otherwise reorganizes. You consent to any and all such Conveyances of your Personal Information.

    Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, we will not sell, trade, or disclose your Personal Information we have collected without your consent.  

    ## 5.  HOW WE PROTECT INFORMATION WE COLLECT

    To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we use appropriate industry-standard procedures to safeguard the confidentially of your Personal Information, such as firewall, encryption, token authentication, application proxies, monitoring technology, and adaptive analysis of network traffic to track abuse of our network and its data. Only a limited number of our employees have access to your information. Any credit card or sensitive information such as social security number or tax ID you supply to us is transmitted and protected via Secure Socket Layer technology and HTTPS protocol. After being transmitted the credit card information is stored in our databases only to be accessed as stated above. However, you should assume that no data transmitted over the Internet can be 100% secure. Therefore, although we believe the measures implemented by us reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved, we do not promise or guarantee, and you should not expect, that your Personal Information or private communications will always remain private. 
    
    If you believe that your username or password has been stolen, you are required to notify us so that necessary measures can be taken immediately. 

    ## 6.  HOW LONG WE KEEP USER INFORMATION

    We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at privacy@prize.com.  We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.  

    ## 7.  SPECIAL NOTE ABOUT CHILDREN

    In order to be eligible to use our Services, you must be at least 18 years of age or older.  We do not currently market to or create special areas for use by children. Accordingly, we do not knowingly collect age identifying information, nor do we knowingly collect any Personal Information from children under the age of 13 years.  However, we hereby advise all visitors to our Website under the age of 13 not to disclose or provide any Personal Information on our Website.  In the event that we discover that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Information to us, in accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (please see the Federal Trade Commission's website at [www.ftc.gov/privacy/privacyinitiatives/childrens.html](http://www.ftc.gov/privacy/privacyinitiatives/childrens.html) for more information about this Act), we will delete the child's Personal Information from our files to the extent technologically possible immediately.

    ## 8.  CONSENT TO TRANSFER

    The Website is operated in the United States. If you are located in the European Union, Canada or elsewhere outside of the United States, please be aware that information we collect will be transferred to and processed in the United States. By using the Website, or providing us with any information, you consent to this transfer, processing and storage of your information in the United States, a jurisdiction in which the privacy laws may not be as comprehensive as those in the country where you reside and/or are a citizen.

    ## 9.  YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

    Residents of the State of California may request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the Personal Information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to: 
    
    Prize, LLC 
    Attn: CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
    P.O. Box 789
    Austin, Texas 78767-0789
    
    For all requests, you must put the statement "Your California Privacy Rights" in the body of your request as well as your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. Please note that we will not accept requests via the telephone, mail, or by facsimile, and we are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or that do not have complete information.

    ## 10.  ACCESS AND UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION

    If you believe that any Personal Information collected and maintained by us about you is not correct or has changed or you wish to delete inaccurate information or your accounts please visit your [Account Edit](http://www.prize.com/account/edit) page. You also may send us an e-mail via our [Support Center](http://www.prize.com/support) explaining the correction or change of the Personal Information we have collected and maintained. We will respond to your access request within 30 days.
    
    In accordance with our routine record keeping, we may delete certain records that contain Personal Information you have submitted through the Website. We are under no obligation to store such Personal Information indefinitely and disclaim any liability arising out of, or related to, the destruction of such Personal Information.
    
    If you ask us to shut down your account or delete your information, we will disable your account within a reasonable period of time. Please note that we may need to retain some information about you in order to satisfy our legal and security obligations. In addition, you should be aware that it is not always possible to completely remove or delete all of your information from our databases without some residual data because of backups and other reasons.

    ## 11.  PERSONAL CHOICE IN THE DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

    If you do not want us to share your Personal Information with our parent, affiliates, subsidiaries and Partners and third party service providers for marketing purposes, or if you do not want to receive certain communications and offers from us You can "opt-out" of such sharing, communications and offers by checking the "opt out" box that will appear next to Your registration form when You register or by following the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of each communication. 
    
    You may also e-mail via our [Support Center](http://www.prize.com/support), or write us at:
    
    Prize, LLC 
    Attn: DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION
    P.O. Box 789
    Austin, Texas 78767-0789
    
    Please note that even if you unsubscribe to promotional offers or other marketing messages, we still may need to send you communications relating to your use of the Website, such as a transaction initiated by you or for other legitimate non-marketing reasons. 

    ## 12.  USER-GENERATED CONTENT

    The Website may enable users to submit their own content for blogs, videos, chat rooms, message boards. private messages, and other functions. Publication of User Generated Content on the Website is subject to our [Terms and Conditions](http://www.prize.com/terms). Any information You disclose in these areas is or may be deemed to be public information and you must exercise caution and discretion before posting any of Your Personal Information. We cannot prevent such information from being used in a manner that may violate this Privacy Policy, the law, or your personal privacy and safety.
    
    Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs, private messages, or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at privacy@prize.com.  In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

    ## 13.  LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEBSITES

    While on the Website or when viewing an email or other content provided by us or the Website, you may encounter links to other websites operated by third parties. These other websites may set their own cookies, collect data or have their own privacy policies and practices. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third party websites and we encourage you to review the privacy policies of these sites as soon as you enter them. Links to any third party website or content do not constitute or imply an endorsement or recommendation by us of the linked website or content. 

    ## 14.  IF YOU HAVE A PRIVACY QUESTION

    If you have a privacy question about our Services, please go to our [Support Center](http://www.prize.com/support).  Or write us at:
    
    Prize, LLC 
    Attn: PRIVACY
    P.O. Box 789
    Austin, Texas 78767-0789
    
    We are committed to working with you to obtain a fair resolution of any privacy concern. 

    ## 15. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

    We reserve the right to change, modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time to reflect changes in our practices and service offerings. If we modify our Privacy Policy, we will update the "Effective Date" and such changes will be effective upon posting. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by prominently posting a notice on the Website or by sending you a notice to the e-mail address we have on file for you. Any revised Privacy Policy will only apply prospectively to Personal Information collected or modified after the Effective Date of the revised policy.  It is your responsibility to periodically check and review our Privacy Policy for changes.
